♪ ♪
WOMAN : Do you like your present ?
BOY : Yeah .
What 's wrong , Michael ?
It reminds me of something .
What ? What does it remind you of ?
Just a dream that I had last night .
What kind of dream ? Was it a good dream or was it a bad dream ?
It was a good dream . A really good dream .
You were dressed in all white , like a ghost .
Like a really beautiful ghost .
You were walking down this white hallway with this big white horse
saying you were gonna come and take me back home .
I wish I could take you home , honey . I miss you there .
- I miss you too . - Aw .
Whenever you look at the horse , you can think of Mommy , okay ?
- Okay . - Okay .
- Are you ticklish ? - No .
- I forgot . I thought you were . - No , I 'm not .
Yes , you are . That 's the face I wanna see .
- Okay ? Cheer up . - Okay .
- All right . - Okay . No more gloom .
- Okay . - Okay .
( GUN CLICKING )
( GUNSHOT )
( WOMAN SCREAMING )
( POLICE SIREN WAILING )
( CLOCK CHIMING )
BRACKETT : Laurie ?
Laurie , is that you ?
Laurie ? Laurie ?
Stop , stop . Stop , stop , sweetie . Stop .
Stop . It 's Sheriff Brackett .
Laurie , give me the gun .
That 's it . Just give me the gun .
That 's it . Easy .
Easy , sweetie . Easy .
I killed him .
( CRYING )
The man .
I climbed in the wall , I fell .
Okay . All right , sweetie .
- Sweetie . It 's okay . - I killed him .
- I killed him . - It 's okay .
It 's all right . It 's all right . It 's all right .
I want you to come with me , okay ?
( SCREAMING )
Please !
What is happening ? Where am I ? Where am I ?
( PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY )
We 're gonna need Neuro , Ortho , Trauma , X-ray !
Am I - - ? Am I gonna die ?
Am I gonna die ? !
BRACKETT : Heads up , everybody . Clear . Make a path .
PARAMEDIC : We 're losing him . Altered mental status ,
unknown injury . BP is 79 over 40 .
DOCTOR : On my count we 're gonna move her . Ready ?
And one , two , three .
( SCREAMING )
DOCTOR : We need CBC chem panel .
Hucks .
How many ?
Two .
They heavy ?
SURGEON 1 : What the hell happened to this kid anyway ?
( CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS )
SURGEON 2 : I don 't know . I thought it was a car accident . I 'm very confused .
SURGEON 1 : At least Neurosurgery cleared her head .
We don 't have to do anything with that .
SURGEON 2 : Right .
She 's gonna need Plastic , but that 's the least of her worries right now .
- Come on . - GARY : Pull me down the stairs .
- HOOKS : Lift up your end . - GARY : Come on , pull it up .
SURGEON 1 : Cut .
OFFICER : On three . Nice and easy . One , two , three !
( OFFICER GRUNTING )
MAN : Let 's go feet first .
HOOKS : Feels like he 's made of lead .
OFFICER : Wait , wait , wait . Pick him up .
MAN : Oh , Jesus Christ .
He weighs a ton .
SURGEON 2 : Looks good .
SURGEON 1 : It 'll hold . At least for now .
Strap him down tight .
I don 't need that behemoth banging around back there .
Yeah , yeah , yeah . This ain 't my first fucking corpse , rodeo .
HOOKS : Just close it up when you 're done .
When the boys get him over to county ,
just make sure that they lock the place up tight .
I don 't want any surprises till I get there in the morning .
No problem . On first sight ,
I 'd say cause of death is fairly obvious .
I 'd say that there 's nothing obvious about anything that happened here tonight .
Not a goddamn thing .
The son of a bitch was heavy , huh ?
Six guys to lift one stiff .
That 's one for the books .
Technically , five guys and a girl .
Whatever .
Did you get a look at the naked chick ?
Ooh .
Man , she was F-I-N-E , fine .
( GARY LAUGHING )
Yeah . She still looked fresh .
I heard a story about a couple of meat wagon boys
fucking corpses over in Essex .
I ain 't never had the urge till tonight .
Whoa , whoa , hey , hey , whoa ! Whoa . Come on !
Brackett even thinks he hears you joking about that
- and you 're out of here on your ass . - I wouldn 't ever do it .
- Oh , yeah ? - I 'm just saying .
She still looked good to me . Nice little titties hanging out .
- Come on , that 's disgusting . Stop it . - I got wood just Ziploc 'ing her up .
Stop . Shut up . Please .
I 'm just saying , man .
- Hey . - Huh ?
What 's the difference between jam and jelly ?
I don 't know . What ?
You can 't jelly your cock up a dead girl 's ass .
- Ha , ha , ha . - Ha , ha . I knew that one .
Cow ! Cow !
( COUGHING )
( GARY GRUNTING )
Shit . Oh , shit .
Oh , fuck . Hooks . Hooks .
Hooks . Hooks .
( GRUNTING )
Fuck ! Fuck ! Fuck !
Fuck ! Fuck . Fuck .
Oh , God .
( MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY )
Fuck . Fuck .
( METAL THUDS )
Fuck !
Oh , fuck !
( THUDS CONTINUE )
Help me ! Help me !
Aah !
Hooks .
Hooks , Hooks , Hooks . Hooks , Hooks .
♪ ♪
Help me . Help please .
Help me .
Help . Help .
Please , help . Help me !
Help me . Hey .
( GRUNTING )
( THUNDER CRASHING )
( THE MOODY BLUES PLAYING NIGHTS IN WHITE SATIN ON TV )
( GRUNTING )
So I told her . I said , " Girl , if you think I 'm letting you handle Thanksgiving ,
- then I 'm ordering Chinese . " - Ha , ha , ha .
Octavia , it 's a pleasure that you 're embracing life this way .
I love seeing you .
DANIELS : She 's bringing Miriam down .
- Not the dog ! - That yapping dog that peed
- all over my new couch . - Ha , ha , ha .
You are gonna have to cook that dog for Thanksgiving .
( BOTH LAUGHING )
Honey , I 'm gonna leave .
- Hold down the fort . - All right , doc .
- MAPLE : I 'll see you tomorrow . - Good night .
LAURIE : Annie ?
Oh , Annie .
Oh , baby .
( CRYING )
Oh , Annie .
Oh , Annie . Please don 't die . Please , please , please don 't die .
DANIELS : Please , Miss Strode .
You cannot be in here .
I just wanted to sit here with her . Please , I won 't bother her .
Mm-mm . You need to go back to your own room .
You need to rest just as much as she does .
Please . Please Just a few minutes . Just a few minutes . Please .
Come on . Let 's get you back into bed .
You 're doing good , sweetie . Doing good . All right .
MAN ( OVER PA ) : Nurse Daniels , please report to Emergency Room A.
Oh . Honey , do you need my help getting back to your room ?
I 'm fine .
MAN : Nurse Daniels , please report to Emergency Room A.
Nurse , I. ...
♪ ♪
I need something for my head .
Hello ?
I 'm getting really dizzy .
( GRUNTING )
Nurse , I need something for my head .
♪ ♪
( SCREAMS )
( SCREAMING )
( WHIMPERING )
( DANIELS SCREAMING )
( DANIELS CRYING )
( MICHAEL GRUNTING AND DANIELS SCREAMING )
♪ ♪
LAURIE : Help !
Help !
Help ! Somebody ! Please !
( SCREAMS )
( WHIMPERING )
Help ! Help !
Help , somebody !
Please !
Help !
Somebody , please .
Help me !
( SCREAMING )
Help !
Help me !
♪ ♪
Oh , goddamn it .
This is just fucking great .
- Help me , please ! Help me ! - Oh , my God !
- What the Christ are you doing here ? - Please help . Help me , please .
BUDDY : You 're gonna freeze your ass off out here .
- LAURIE : Please ! Please ! Please ! - Here , easy .
- Look , just sit down . Here , here . - LAURIE : Please !
Here , now . Put this on before they blame me for you catching pneumonia .
The nurse is dead . The nurse is - -
No , no , it 's going to be okay . Listen , it 's going to be all right .
I work here . My name is Buddy .
- Okay , it 's going to be fine . - No . No , it 's not .
- I 've gotta get you back . - No , it 's - - No , it 's - -
- Just let me go get my car , okay ? - Please ! Please !
- It 'll just take a second . - No , no !
No , honey , it 'll just take a second .
- Please don 't leave me . Please . - The car is right out there .
Look , look , here . Here , here .
Just drink what 's left of this till I get back , okay ?
Okay ? And I promise , I 'll be back in just a second .
- LAURIE : No , please . - BUDDY : Okay , just don 't - -
Nobody 's gonna hurt you , honey .
It 'll be all right . Here , I 'm gonna lock this door , okay ?
One second ,
and then I will pull up right here , okay ?
All right .
LAURIE : Buddy !
Buddy , please .
Buddy , please come back !
( THE MOODY BLUES PLAYING NIGHTS IN WHITE SATIN )
Buddy !
( PANTING )
BUDDY : I 'm sorry .
This old car doesn 't always like to start ,
especially in the rain .
Everything will be fine , okay ?
( LAURIE SCREAMS )
No ! Buddy !
( BUDDY GRUNTING )
( LAURIE SCREAMING )
( MICHAEL GRUNTING )
Somebody ! Somebody , please !
Help me ! Help me , please !
( SCREAMS )
No !
( PANTING )
Come on .
He 's dead .
He 's fucking dead .
Oh , fuck .
Oh , God .
I am running ragged this morning .
- Morning . - Running ragged .
Good morning .
- Did you hear Laurie last night ? - Yes , Dad .
I hear her every night . Please , God , don 't say anything to her .
I won 't . I won 't .
Want some egg whites ?
No . I think I 'm gonna get me one of them sticky buns on the way in .
That 's great . Pastry for breakfast .
Seriously , 500 calories of sugar and shit .
I know it , I know it .
- LAURIE : Morning . - ANNIE : Morning .
BRACKETT : Good morning , sunshine .
- I got to go . - Hey , slow your roll for one second .
Please do not forget to pick up the pizza .
And whole-wheat crust .
God , Annie .
Why don 't we just have them take the cheese and put it on cardboard ?
- Aren 't you late ? - Cardboard 's got a lot of fiber .
- And it 's cheap . - No meat .
ANNIE : Rough night ?
Did you hear me ?
Mm . Just a little .
God . Just when I think I can get back to something as simple as sleep , it 's like ...
( GRUNTS )
right back at me .
Do you wanna tell me about it ?
Nah .
I don 't remember much .
It was a hospital one .
I haven 't had one of those in a while .
Guess I know what I 'll be yakking about in therapy today .
One day at a time , babe .
One day at a time .
One fucking day at a time .
You know what , if I hear that fucking phrase one more fucking time - -
She just fucking sits there in her fucking leather chair and judges me ...
- like she 's fucking God . - It 's her job , Laurie . My God .
What am I supposed to say ? Boo-fucking-hoo for you .
See ? You don 't fucking care .
Right , I don 't fucking care . I don 't understand , Laurie .
Oh , nice . Thanks for leaving me some coffee , Dad .
♪ ♪
I don 't know , I just - - I wake up and I feel like I can 't even breathe .
Mm-hm .
They seem to be getting worse .
I 'm - - I 'm concerned ,
but , gosh , I can 't say that I 'm surprised .
I mean , it 's Halloween , and Halloween is a big trigger point for you , isn 't it ?
Barbara ,
I know Michael Myers is dead .
I shot him in the fucking head .
I know he 's not gonna come back just because of some stupid holiday .
- Laurie , they never found his body . - So ?
So it 's very hard for you to get closure on this .
I mean , he 's objectively dead but he 's living in your mind ,
and he 's living in your heart and your emotions .
So that 's the reality that we have to heal you from .
Which is why I say you 're still in recovery .
So , basically , I just have to wait until my brain heals ?
Well , let 's try and help your brain heal a little bit today , okay ?
- Okay . - Okay .
How 's your relationship with Annie going ?
- Annie ? - Yeah .
Not good .
Hm .
I don 't know , I feel kind of shitty by saying this , but - -
She 's a constant reminder .
Every time I see her face , and I see those scars ,
I know that it 's my fault .
And I get angry . And there 's something in my body that snaps .
And I get this zero to a hundred rage , and I just wanna go up to her ,
- and I just wanna - - Fuck , I don 't know . - Finish the thought .
- Finish that thought . It 's important . - I 'd rather not . You 'll send me away .
I would never send you away . We 're here to keep you out of the hospital .
The last place you 're gonna heal is in a hospital .
( SIGHS )
What is that ?
That ? That 's whatever you think it is is what that is .
The theory is that this ambiguous stimuli here will bring
your subconscious thoughts into the light . Illuminate them .
So , what do you see ?
White horse .
So , what does that tell you ? Am I crazy or sane ?
It tells me you 're a girl who likes white horses .
♪ ♪
( HORN HONKING )
NANCY : The natives are getting restless .
You were supposed to be here 45 minutes ago .
( PHONE RINGS )
LOOMIS : Hello . Yes , hello , darling .
No . How are you ? Hello ? Hello ?
Damn . Hello ? Argh .
Everybody has been completely briefed on why we are here .
They know the drill so I don 't foresee any problems in that department .
Everything is kosher , as my people say .
I know every one of these journalists personally , they 're cool .
Trust me , they are cool .
So I feel like this should be really a positive experience ,
you know , and be really good for the book .
Whoa . Hi . Did you just mention " journalists , " cool and " positive "
all in the same sentence without throwing up ?
Yes , why ? Is that a problem ?
It 's just quite an oxymoron , my dear .
Look , can you just level with me ?
Is there going to be a problem today ?
You are quite an odd one , aren 't you ?
I mean , look at you . Are you color-coordinated ?
Pink clogs and this orange thing . Are you a clam digger or something ?
I don 't mean that in a lesbian sense .
- I think you mean " carpet muncher . " - I 'm not judging . I 'm not - -
- Hello . - Can we just not get personal ?
Look at this . No !
Look , it 's the wrong photograph !
I mean , this is old Loomis . This is new .
Yes , well , old Loomis increases sales by 25 percent , okay ? So just - -
I 'm not going in there until you go get me
a cup of PG tips with a splash of milk , and I want it sizzling hot .
PG what ?
Tea ?
We don 't have time .
Fine . Fine , I 'll go find you some .
- LOOMIS : Two percent . - NANCY : Two percent .
( AMERAROCKER 'S " SCREAM " PLAYS )
Wow , the princess of punctuality is a little late .
Alert the authorities . Laurie has been replaced by a pod .
Whoa , wait , I 'm early . I worked overtime last night .
Oh . See , you 're too together . No , you gotta loosen up a little , babe .
You know , bring some anarchy to the party .
So you 're saying I can start showing up whenever I want ?
Not on my dime , sister .
You can save the slacker shit
for those corporate bloodsuckers who can afford it .
That 's why we 're going down the toilet .
Since 1946 , this country has been under the military-industrial - -
- Fuck the man . - Right on , sister .
You 're really interested . I know , I know .
( MYA CHUCKLES )
MEAT : I give in . You win . The old man caves again .
- What 's up with him ? - I don 't know .
Are you gonna come and rock balls
with Harley and me at the Phantom Jam or what ?
Hells yeah .
But I 'm not sure if I 'm down with the whole costume concept .
What ? Okay , wait . Think of it like this .
It 's so lame that it 's totally cool again .
LAURIE : Well , I still like my idea better .
What up , dick-lickers ?
Could you please convince Miss Too-Coolio-for-Schoolio
that our costume idea is totally rad ?
Dude , suck it up , ho .
We got a fucking theme going on . Don 't screw it up .
Plus we got you that sick maid outfit
and dudes dig the domestic .
Come on , you guys , it 's borderline drama-class nerd .
- Yeah . Own it . - All right . What do I have to do ?
Stand on this chair and show the old hippie dude my tits again ?
- MYA : No . - HARLEY : Oh , Meat !
- Check out my lady lumps ! - LAURIE : No , no , no .
I 'll wear it . Put down your fucking shirt .
HARLEY : You give in too easy .
All right , you guys ready for it ?
- LAURIE : For what ? - Are you ready ?
- Kick out the jams , motherfucker ! - Whoo !
( MC5 'S " KICK OUT THE JAMS " PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS )
LOOMIS ( ON RECORDING ) : Michael , I 'm sorry to tell you this ,
but your mother has passed away .
She 'll be back .
No , I 'm afraid she won 't be coming to see you anymore .
I 'll see her again , but I won 't see you .
ANNOUNCER : Ladies and gentlemen , Dr. Samuel Loomis ,
author of The Devil Walks Among Us , in stores October 31st .
Thank you all and welcome .
I think you can all see quite clearly here
that Michael 's psychotic perception
is in complete denial about his own mother 's suicide
Freud would certainly have a field day with that little one , wouldn 't he ?
( LOOMIS CROWD CHUCKLE )
So it is the fate of all of us
to direct our first sexual impulses towards our mothers
and our first murderess hatred against our fathers .
Now , in Michael 's case , I became the surrogate father .
The last father in a long series of fathers .
Well , um , has anybody got any questions at all ?
Yes , sir . Yes . Please .
Um , you never really made it clear whether you believe it was nurture or nature
that contributed to Michael 's condition .
I would like to answer it , in part , by quoting
the great George Bernard Shaw ,
with a little Loomis twist at the end .
He says : " In the arts of life , man invents nothing .
But in the arts of death , he outdoes nature herself
and produces , by chemistry and machinery ,
all the slaughter of plague , pestilence , famine "
and Michael Myers .
( LAUGHS )
Well , sorry , but I like that little one .
That 's my own little twist .
Yes , ma 'am ?
Do you feel personally responsible for the deaths of as many as 15 victims ?
I have tremendous sympathy for all the families involved .
And do I personally feel responsible ? Ma 'am , no , I do not .
And I 've said that many times .
It 's just awful and , um ,
I was very nearly a victim myself .
I 'm not a psychic Sherlock Holmes playing Superman .
Since the authorities haven 't been able to produce a body ,
do you think Michael is alive or dead ?
WOMAN : Will he kill again ?
Here we go again .
( MOUTHING )
Look , let me make things nice and sparkling clear .
Michael Myers is fucking dead !
Now , do you brain-dead gossip mongers
want me to spell it out for you ? D-E-A-D !
♪ ♪
DEBORAH : Michael .
Halloween is coming .
You have to get ready .
We are counting on you to bring us home this year .
I won 't let you down .
DEBORAH : I know you won 't , baby .
I love you , Mama .
DEBORAH : I love you too , Michael .
( COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS )
MAN : It 's that same guy who 's been coming .
You seen him before ?
WOMAN : Yeah , it 's the same filthy bum .
- MAN : Stealing our shit . - I 'd recognize him anywhere , Daddy .
Motherfucker .
Can 't have drifters just coming in here and taking whatever they want .
What y 'all gonna do ?
Hey . Hey , hey , hey .
( DOG BARKING )
Shut up , Ivan . We see him .
Let 's do it .
DAUGHTER : You 're just gonna scare him .
- Daddy , what the fuck ? - Safety .
Hey , you stupid , slimy dick .
I told you if you came on this land again , I 'd beat the fuck out of you .
What the fuck you think you 're doing here ?
SON : As big as he is dumb , man .
Look at that . He 's about 7-foot of fuck-tard .
FATHER : I 'm talking to you , shit-heel .
You stupid fuck !
I 'm talking to you !
SON : What 's wrong with this son of a bitch ?
Give him a taste of that here .
( SON GRUNTING )
FATHER : All right .
DAUGHTER : Hey ! No ! You 'll fucking kill him .
FATHER : Wanna go to jail for killing that fucking turd ?
SON : One more shot . Shut up !
SON : Woo-hoo-hoo .
DAUGHTER : Chris , knock it off .
- FATHER : Big man . - SON : Oh , man .
- DAUGHTER : Come on , Daddy . - Don 't you come back , son of a bitch .
Man , that was a professional ass-whupping there .
Oh , I 'm jacked .
Whoo !
- DAUGHTER : You okay ? - Shut up , Ivan !
I 'm so sorry . What are we gonna do , just fucking leave him out here ?
Get in the truck .
Come on now . Chop-chop .
- Get in the truck . - I 'm so sorry .
I am so sorry .
♪ ♪
FATHER : Shut up , Ivan .
- SON : Whoo . - DAUGHTER : Seriously .
- SON : Jump up . - You didn 't need to
fucking beat him to a pulp .
- SON : I told the guy . - DAUGHTER : Fuck that .
( SON GRUNTING )
Oh , my God !
FATHER : Fuck !
( FATHER GRUNTING )
DAUGHTER : No , Daddy !
( FATHER AND DAUGHTER SCREAMING )
( SCREAMING )
What are you doing ? I said I was fucking sorry !
( MICHAEL GRUNTING )
( DOG BARKING )
LAURIE : Pizza .
- Dude , you didn 't get whole wheat . - I forgot .
Mm-hm .
Anybody hungry ?
- Starving like Marvin . - BRACKETT : Starving like Marvin .
Has anybody at this table ever wondered
who Marvin is ?
I mean , the original Marvin who was starving Marvin ?
- What ? - Was it - - ? Was it Lee Marvin ?
Who 's Lee Marvin ?
Did I stutter ?
Paint Your Wagon . The Professionals . Lee Marvin .
Cat Ballou ?
Cat Ballou . He was great in Cat Ballou .
I can 't believe you guys haven 't seen it . He was , like , playing this drunk ,
but he 's , like , the greatest gun in the West .
At one point he 's , like ,
talking about being a gunslinger .
Bam . And he misses the barn .
He misses the barn completely .
I wanna thank the both of you for making me feel as old as Methuselah .
All I know is I hope that dead , rotting flesh didn 't bump on my pineapple .
A little dead , rotting flesh never hurt anybody .
Oh , God . Do we have to do this every fucking time we eat together ?
We need to get you off the animal products , Mr. B.
- ANNIE : Not gonna happen . - Man was meant to eat meat .
We , all of us , have a little bit of caveman in us .
( GRUNTING )
ANNIE : God .
How is it possible that every father
perfects the art of humiliating their offspring ?
What ? It 's cute .
Mm-hm .
( GRUNTS )
- What ? - Come on , Annie .
I 'll go . I always go .
( SIGHS )
( GRUNTING )
ANNIE : Hang on .
God .
- Here . - Thanks .
Sorry I was such a bitch earlier .
I get it .
Okay .
♪ ♪
Where have you been ? I 've been waiting .
You know I can 't come here anymore .
My time here is over .
- You 're here now . - Michael ,
you know I 'm not really here .
I wanna show you something .
All right .
I found her .
I found Boo .
My baby .
Can we be a family again ?
Not yet , Michael .
Not yet .
( SCREAMING )
( PANTING )
Oh , fuck .
Come here , buddy .
WENDY : So , Dr. Loomis , tell me .
How long do you plan on staying in town ?
Please . Sam .
Thank you . Well , I could stay a few extra days .
It depends on if there 's something or someone that motivated me .
NANCY : Excuse me , Dr. Loomis - -
We 're in - - I 'm in the middle of something .
Could I speak to you for a second ? Please ?
- What ? - Please ?
Excuse me , my dear . I won 't be one second .
What ?
Okay , I am all for selling books . All right ?
God knows I 've done some things that I 'm not proud of ,
but this is disgusting . I did not agree to this backdrop .
I mean , what 's next ? Heading over to the cemetery
and dancing on the victims ' graves ?
Look , I don 't think you quite understand
- what I 'm trying to accomplish here . - Well , fair enough . I don 't .
Please , explain it to me . I would really like to understand .
I 'm selling the sizzle , not the steak .
- The sizzle ? - Yes .
The sizzle . It 's bad taste is what it is .
It 's just gonna add fuel to the lynch mob fire .
Bad taste ? Bad taste ?
My God , it 's business , woman ! Business .
Besides , bad taste is the petrol that drives the American dream .
Well , I think it 's a mistake .
- Oh , yeah , you do , do you ? - Yes .
Well , when I want your opinion , I 'll beat it out of you .
Here . Now , take that and go sit in the car . Go on . Get your ass in there .
LOOMIS : Okay . Hi , where do you want me ?
( MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON RADIO )
♪ ♪
( LAURIE SCREAMS )
LAURIE : Die , you fucking bitch !
You fucking bitch ! I 'm gonna fucking kill you .
I 'm gonna fuck you - - Rip your fucking throat .
Fucking die , you fucking bitch !
You fucking cunt !
Fucking bitch !
Please , Laurie , please !
You fucking - - Die , you fucking bitch !
( ANNIE SCREAMING )
Laurie ! Laurie , Laurie , Laurie !
( SCREAMS )
( GASPING )
( WHIMPERING )
( SOBBING )
♪ ♪
Argh !
- LOU : You guys like Frankenstein ? - KIDS : Yes .
LOU : Who likes popcorn ?
LAURIE : So I was going through the park ,
and there was this really crazy Frankenstein .
And he was , like , yelling at the kids .
And he was yelling at them , like , perverted things and stuff .
And I really thought it was funny and I stopped and watched .
And then I saw this , like , farm .
- BARBARA : Laurie ? - And this lady let me hold the pig .
BARBARA : What are you feeling right now , Laurie ?
The pig really liked me and she said that the pig
- Laurie ? - liked me . I wanted to take it home .
Sit down , Laurie .
Come on , Laurie .
Stay centered . What 's going on ?
I had this really , really , really crazy attack .
And not while I was asleep , while I was awake .
Look , I just need you to prescribe me something , please .
Laurie , according to my notes , you should have a lot of medication .
I don 't . I 'm out .
Look , I need you to get your magic pen and your magic piece of paper ,
and I need you to write me up a prescription , please .
Laurie , that 's not the answer . Are you doing your breathing exercises ?
- Breathing exercises ? - Yes , it helps .
- Breathing exercises aren 't gonna cut it . - They help , Laurie .
- And I can 't deal with this ! - Oh , honey .
I 'm not strong enough and I 'm tired of pretending that I am .
Look , Laurie , listen to me . Stay with me .
You are so much stronger than you think you are . You are .
- Now , go on , sit down . Sit down . - You better fucking let me go
and give me some fucking prescriptions !
I 'm gonna give you some Haldol to tide you over .
- Haldol ? - Yes , Haldol .
- It 'll take some of these thoughts away . - I don 't want Haldol .
- I want my prescription ! - I 'm so sorry you 're going through this .
Fuck , you know what ?
Fuck you and fuck this !
I 'm tired of your : How are you , Laurie ?
I 'm so concerned at 100 bucks an hour . "
You know what ? I would be fucking concerned at 100 bucks an hour .
- I 'm really concerned right now . - Bullshit .
- No , it 's not bullshit . - You 're more fucked up than I am ,
you crazy bitch !
♪ ♪
WENDY : ( ON TV ) For most of us , Michael Myers is a mysterious legend of evil .
But for Dr. Samuel Loomis ,
the bogeyman is all too real .
There have been wild rumors circulating as to the content of your new book .
- What can you tell me ? - Well ,
after my last encounter with Michael ,
some startling facts came to light ,
and I just thought that the public really ought to know .
WENDY : Such as ?
Read the book , as they say .
But weren 't you horrified when the news broke that Michael 's body went missing ?
LOOMIS : No , not really .
How you can lose a body , you know , transporting it from A to B.
You better ask the sheriff 's department that one . Heh , heh , heh .
WENDY : Well , do you think that the body will reappear ?
Yes , probably . You know , somewhere it 'll reappear ,
along with the Elephant Man 's bones at some sideshow .
But as my old Aunt Miri used to say :
" Freaks will always find their way home . "
( ROCKABILLY MUSIC PLAYING ON TV )
What 's up with the booze ?
Oh , yeah . Meet my new best friend .
Oh , is this how your new work friends roll ?
Maybe . Jealous ?
- Whatever . - You know what Annie ?
I don 't need your shit .
You don 't need my shit ?
You don 't need my shit ? I put up with your shit , 24-7 .
You better back the fuck off !
Or what , huh ? The fuck are you gonna do ?
You know what , you act like you 're the only one whose life got fucking trashed .
I 'm so not buying the new Laurie act .
I 'm not putting up with your moaning shit .
Get the fuck out of my room ! Get the fuck out of my room !
I 'm not impressed .
Fuck !
( ROD STEWART 'S I 'M LOSING YOU PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS )
Hey , Howard .
Can 't afford the new tits . Can you loan me some bones ? "
Fucking whore .
LOU : Hey ! Hey , Misty , come here .
Come on , it 's on . Come on , it 's finally on .
I 'm on TV . You 're missing it . Move your ass . Come here . Look at this !
MISTY : Oh , my God , baby .
Ha , ha , ha . Look at that . I 'm incredible .
( ON TV ) - - the smile you 'll have on your face at the Rabbit In Red Lounge
when you come and you see some of my girls dance because they are fantastic .
LOU : Hey , Howard , where are those drinks ?
( LOU LAUGHS AND HOWARD CHUCKLES )
HOWARD : Hey , boss . That 's right , they love you , man .
- That 's why the whole town loves you . - LOU : Yeah , they love me .
They love me like cancer , that 's how much they love me .
You look like that big guy .
( GRUNTING )
The shit falls on his head .
Grandfather , I 'm mad , I 'm pissed off .
Hey , where 's my daughter with the cans and the blond hair and the - - ? "
LOU : What are you talking about ?
Yeah . Green makes you look sexy , baby .
( LOU CHUCKLES )
Green . That suits you , man .
It really suits you . It 's like the color of money . Ka-ching .
- MISTY : Dumbass . - Ha-ha-ha .
LOU : Hey , Howard , let me ask you a question .
I got a riddle for you .
What does a stripper do with her asshole before she dances .
I don 't know .
She gives him 10 bucks and she tells him to take out the trash !
( MISTY HOWARD LAUGHING )
- That 's a good one . - Here , Howard . Take out the trash .
Take out the trash , Howard .
MISTY : He 's good at taking out the trash .
Ha-ha-ha . I 'm funny .
Yeah , I 'm the big joke .
Hey , I 'm on TV . Quiet . Shut up . Shut up .
Enjoy the fucking herpes , old man .
- LOU : I got an aura . - MISTY : You got an aura , baby .
LOU : You have an aura . You got two auras .
- MISTY : You 're so bad . - LOU : Heh , heh . Really ?
- MISTY : Auras are popping out . - LOU : Ha ! Let me see those auras .
HOWARD : Two-faced bitch .
Fucking Hoss . I 'm fucking Hop Sing doing all the chores .
You bitch .
Yeah , Howard .
Can I have some money for my dad 's blood transfusion ? "
What the fuck you doing , man ,
sneaking around back here ?
♪ ♪
Hey .
The boss don 't like you bums hanging out back here ,
rooting around through the Dumpsters .
So get a move on .
Look , man .
Don 't give me no reason .
I already sent some sorry fucking jag-off
to the emergency room tonight .
So
I suggest you take the easy road out
and hit the bricks , Dorothy .
Heh , fu ...
Trust me ,
you filthy , dirty hippie ,
you don 't wanna be doing that .
Copy that , downtown ?
( GRUNTS )
Fuck .
( HOWARD GRUNTING )
( MICHAEL GRUNTING )
♪ ♪
DEBORAH : We 're done waiting .
Only a river of blood can bring us back together .
It 's up to you .
It 's always been up to you , Michael .
Hey , baby , you know what ? It 's after midnight .
So ? I don 't think my pussy is gonna turn into a pumpkin .
It 's technically Halloween , baby .
How 'd you like to be fucked by the Frankenstein monster , huh ?
( BOTH LAUGHING )
- You 're my bride of Frankenstein . - Oh , ooh .
Big , green , scary monster !
Oh , no . Oh , I 'm so scared .
- Ha , ha , ha . Titties good . - No .
Ass good .
♪ ♪
I 'm gonna give it to you good .
I 'm gonna give you my jolly green giant .
Jesus Christ !
What are you doing ? Get the fuck out of here .
Come on , get the fuck out of here , motherfucker .
You 're gonna stare me down ?
Stare this down , motherfucker !
Come on now ! I 'll fucking blow two holes right through your fucking mask .
I been to Nam . I 'll take you out .
You hear me ? I 'll fucking - -
( MISTY SCREAMING )
( SOBBING )
( LOU SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY )
LOU : What are you doing ?
( SCREAMING )
Open the door ! No !
No ! Open the door !
( MISTY SCREAMING )
Son of a bitch !
You fucking did it !
Fuck , what am I gonna do ?
( PHONE RINGING )
- Hello ? - BRACKETT : Hey , princess .
Hey , Dad . What 's up ?
Listen , is , uh , Laurie around ?
I 'd like to talk to her .
No , she left before I got up . Why , what 's up ?
Well , could you do me a favor ?
Could you find her and then call me when you do ?
Why ? What 's going on ?
Uh , sweetie , I gotta tell you about that later .
Could you just do me that favor , please ?
- Everything okay ? - Everything is fine .
I just need to talk to her , sweetie . Okay ?
♪ ♪
He 's still out there .
Rich and famous . All because of our pain .
DEBORAH : I hope he 's having fun .
Are you a real redhead ? Thank you . Have a good one .
- Here you go . - Thanks .
LOOMIS : It 's going very well , indeed . Well done .
Yes , look at the crowd . It 's great . Great .
Right , well done .
- Ah . Thank you . - Can you make it out to , uh - - ?
- I 'm sorry , I 'm a little nervous . Chett . - Calm down , calm down .
- Big deep breath . - Thanks .
Chett Johns . No , no , actually , you know what ?
- Chett , the bringer of death . - Okay .
That 's Chett with two T 's .
- Chett , the bringer of ... - The bringer of
death . Oh , man , that is so awesome .
- There you go . - Thank you . Look ,
I just wanted to let you know
that Michael is so much deeper than those other guys .
Like Dahmer and that bitch Bundy
because he eats at the core of the victim 's soul , you know ?
- How people ostracize those - - - All right . Well , thanks so much .
- You 're the man . You 're the man . - You 're the man !
- All right . Thank you . - You 're the man , dude .
- You 're awesome . Thank you . - NANCY : Thank you .
( WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY )
LOOMIS : Jesus . Well , we always have one , don 't we ?
( LAUGHING )
Hi . How are you ?
Ah . Oh .
Do you want me to sign this ? What ?
You don 't recognize her ?
- Um ... Why ? Should I ? - I 'm not surprised .
Ahem . Take a really good look at her .
- Oh , she 's beautiful . - She was beautiful .
- This is my daughter . - Mm-hm .
Lynda .
- Your monster killed her . - Whoa , whoa , whoa , wait .
- He butchered her . - You have my deepest sympathy .
Do I have your deepest sympathy , you fucking pig ?
- I 'm truly sorry . - You killer .
- No , I didn 't kill anyone . - You killer !
All right , everyone , just calm down . It 's all right .
You butchered my baby . Back up !
You butchered my baby !
- NANCY : Can we get somebody - - ? - KYLE : I 'm gonna get you , Loomis .
I swear - - Get your hands off me . Get your goddamn hands off me !
It 's all right . Everyone , just calm down . Calm down .
- All right , I 'm fine . - LOOMIS : Everything 's under control .
- You son of a bitch ! - NANCY : He 's got a gun !
- KYLE : I 'm gonna kill you , Loomis ! - LOOMIS : Jesus .
I 'm gonna kill you , goddamn it !
NANCY : I mean , the police said that it wasn 't even loaded , so - -
LOOMIS : Oh , I feel so much better .
All part of the job , I suppose .
Spoon-feeding drivel to the masses .
Comes with its own bloody price , doesn 't it ?
If you say so .
Just what is that tone , Miss McDonald ?
Do you think I 'm crossing the line or something ?
I mean , do please feel free to voice your opinion .
Well , off the record , yes .
Yes , actually , I think this book crosses quite a few lines .
These are people 's lives you 're toying with .
There 's gonna be serious repercussions .
♪ ♪
( CRYING )
Fuck .
Fuck !
Fuck ! Fuck !
Fuck you , motherfucker !
Fuck !
Fucker !
( ROCK MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS )
ANNIE : Laurie ?
Hey . Hey !
( LAURIE CRYING )
What is - - ? Hey , where are you going ?
I 'm getting the fuck out of here .
Wait . Wait , hey ! Listen , my dad called . He was trying to find you .
Yeah , I bet he was .
Tell me you didn 't know , please !
- Tell me you didn 't know . - ANNIE : Know what ?
Fuck it . I mean , daddy 's little princess knows all , right ?
What are you talking about ?
Hey , stop . Calm down . Look at me .
What is going on ?
Let me just call my dad , okay ? We can talk to him .
You know what ? I have a message for your dad .
Tell him that Angel says fuck you !
ANNIE : Who is Angel ? Laurie !
( DIAMOND HEAD 'S " AM I EVIL ? " PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS )
Hey , fucking asshole !
Fuck you !
Hey , sweetie , did you find her ?
Yes . She ran in and she ran out screaming some shit about :
Tell your dad that Angel says " fuck you . "
( OVER PHONE ) Who the fuck is Angel ?
Fuck , fuck , fuck .
I want you to head over to my house and keep an eye on Annie for me . Okay ?
Oh , boss , last year she tried to kick me in the nuts .
You know she 's not gonna like this .
I don 't care what she likes .
Now head over to my place , and if she kicks you out ,
you just sit outside with a shotgun on your lap ,
- like you did last year , all right ? - Yes .
( ROCK MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS )
Look , um , can I crash here tonight , please ?
MYA : Yeah , okay .
What 's up ?
Look , I just found something out that 's kind of
freaking me the fuck out .
Okay . What is it ?
See , I went into this bookstore ,
and I got this book and
inside there 's just a bunch of pictures - -
Check me out , man .
Fucking sick , huh ? Whoo .
I 'm a chick dressing up as a dude who wants to be a chick .
- Shut up . - What ? Who died ?
( CRYING )
Shit , baby , did somebody really die ?
I 'm not me .
I 'm not me . Do you understand what the fuck I 'm saying ?
- Not really . - But - -
Who are you then ?
I 'm Angel Myers .
Michael Myers ' sister .
Heh . All right , dude , even I wouldn 't fucking touch that joke .
You can 't kid around about that shit . You had me going there .
- You 're such a good little actress - - - I am not fucking joking !
All right , if you fucking think I 'm lying , look at this .
All right ? Look .
There 's me , Angel Myers .
And here 's my fucked-up life .
Fuck .
Maybe it 's a mistake .
HARLEY : Holy shit , dude .
This is fucking insane .
Our next guest gained infamy as a psychologist
for America 's leading serial killer .
Leading serial killer ? Well , he 's probably the most notorious .
Leading ? He 's number one in his field .
Anyway , his new book is called The Devil Walks Among Us
is available somewhere . Please welcome Dr. Samuel Loomis .
( BAND PLAYING AND AUDIENCE CLAPPING )
- Dr . Loomis . - Hi , David . How are you ?
- Have a seat . - Hi , everyone . Nice to , uh - -
Thank you . Thank you . Very nice .
- Mr . Weird , how are you ? - AI 's good .
Great .
Now , you 've been criticized , and in some circles , I gotta say ,
outright accused of profiteering off the misery of others .
I mean , how do you even respond to that criticism ?
Well , you know , I think that 's completely unfounded .
I always get permission when I do the parody .
No , Al , I was talking to Loomis .
Oh , I 'm sorry . Go ahead .
No , no , no , please . It was fascinating , your answer .
- Your turn . I 'm done . - LOOMIS : If you 've got something ...
Ahem . Actually , I take great issue with that statement .
Besides , I might say that I 've endured quite a lot of misery of my own
in order to tell this story .
Yeah , everyone feels real bad for you except - -
LOOMIS : I have never , ever been so humiliated in all my life !
NANCY : You were fantastic . Trust me .
- Nonsense ! Good night . Thank you . - Thank you .
♪ ♪
- BOY 1 : Trick or treat . - WOMAN : Here you go .
- BOY 2 : Thank you . - BOY 1 : Thank you .
Are you a giant ?
Can we be friends ?
Mark , come on . Don 't talk to strangers .
Bye .
LAURIE : I wanna party . I 've spent my whole fucking life being good
and look where it 's gotten me .
Fucking nowhere .
Fuck it , you guys .
Are you guys with me or not ?
I just - - I think that we should stay back .
I mean , what you need is a mellow night .
- No , I don 't . - Yeah , definitely . We can just
watch TV or something .
Yeah , like , order some food
and figure all this shit out .
I want ...
to go party !
I wanna fucking get drunk . I don 't fucking care anymore .
I want to fucking party !
- I wanna party . - Well , you know me . I 'm totally in .
Come on , she wants to party .
- Please ? - Oh , please ?
Come on . Come on , boo-boo , please ?
All right , all right , all right . Fine .
- Has to be a chill night , though . - Okay , a chill night .
( CAPTAIN CLEGG AND THE NIGHT CREATURES PLAYING TRANSYLVANIA TERROR TRAIN )
( PEOPLE CHATTERING )
( MAN SINGING TRANSYLVANIA TERROR TRAIN )
What the fuck ? Andy , are you seriously planning on standing out here all night ?
- This is ridiculous . - Hey , Annie ,
I just do what the boss tells me .
Well , I 'm the boss of the boss ,
and I say move your shitbox over there , Kojak . Okay ?
And don 't make a federal case out of it . Turn off the damn gumballs .
I 'll do what I gotta do .
What the fuck are you gonna do , jackhole ?
- ANDY : You 'll find out . - Oh . Ooh , I 'll find out ?
Ooh . I 'm shaking in my boots .
( CROWD CHEERING )
Okay , why don 't we get back to the music .
I get another drink .
( CROWD CHEERING )
Good idea , huh ?
Let 's go . Captain Clegg and the Night Creatures .
( CHEERING )
( PLAYING MACON COUNTY MORGUE )
MAN : Yeah !
( SINGING MACON COUNTY MORGUE )
( CHUCKLING )
- HARLEY : Do you like my outfit ? - MAN : I do , I do .
What are you supposed to be ? A sexy vampire ?
HARLEY : I 'm a chick who 's dressing up as a dude who wants to be a chick .
MAN : But you are a chick , though , right ?
Watch your step .
HARLEY : Why don 't you put your hands down my pants and find out , Wolfman ?
MAN : At this point I don 't really care . No , but seriously , you have a vagina ?
( MAN HOWLS AND HARLEY CHUCKLES )
HARLEY : You 're so cute .
MAN : You 're gonna like my van , though , I promise .
- You got a fucking van ? - Yeah . I got a van .
It 's got some drinks in there . They 're roofie-free , I swear .
HARLEY : A " blowjob " ? Is that what you guys call them still ?
I call them " sucking a dick . "
- MAN : There she is . She 's a beauty . - She is , isn 't she ?
MAN : I had a lot of fun in this van . And a lot of pussy .
The Shaggin ' Wagon .
It 's a work of art . I like her - -
What 's the difference between a jack-o ' - lantern and a blond ?
CROWD : What ?
There is no difference .
They both have a blank expression , and they 're hollow inside .
( LAUGHS THEN HOWLS )
( BOOS )
I like them , you know what I mean ? You shut the lights off , they glow .
The ladies seem to like it .
Yeah ? The ladies love it ?
Yeah . Yeah , yeah .
- You get laid a lot ? - I get a good amount .
Hey , hold this , Blondie .
Now Blondie and jack-o ' - lantern both have three holes .
( LAUGHING )
Hey , Gianova , do the trick . Heh-heh .
Watch this . Wow .
( CROWD CHEERING AND COFFINS HOWLS )
I love it .
You look very pretty tonight , by the way . Very pretty .
I like your tattoos . Are they real ?
- Oh , yeah . They 're real . - They 're real ? That 's cool .
- I was thinking about getting - - - These are real too .
They are real . May I ? That 's - - They feel real .
- That 's - - That 's nice . That 's nice . - That 's it ?
( FAKES CRYING )
( CHEERING )
You big baby !
Go home !
- Talking 's not working , okay ? - I 'll shut up .
I 'm gonna shut up .
( FOGHAT 'S " I JUST WANT TO MAKE LOVE TO YOU " PLAYS )
Okay , look . Time out , time out . I 'll be right back .
I 'll be right back . Give me one second .
- Where the fuck are you going ? - I gotta take a piss .
I 've had to pee since I got here .
I 'll be right back . Don 't go anywhere .
So who says I wasn 't into the water sports ?
A little golden shower .
That 's gross . You 're a trip . I 'll be right back . I 'll be right back .
Hurry the fuck up .
Fucking hurry up , dude .
( URINE SPLASHING )
♪ ♪
HARLEY : Oh , my God .
No ! No ! No !
Oh , my God . No !
( HARLEY SCREAMING )
( CAPTAIN CLEGG AND THE NIGHT CREATURES PLAYING MACON COUNTY MORGUE )
( CROWD CHEERING AND WHOOPING )
DAVID ( ON TV ) : Welcome Dr. Samuel Loomis .
LOOMIS : Thank you , thank you .
Dr. Donald Faber who 's a noted abnormal psychologist - -
He 's not noted .
He says , " Nothing more than a bloody horror show
showcasing Dr. Loomis ' own self-inflated ego
and never-ending quest for fame and fortune . "
YANKOVIC : Put that in your scrapbook .
DAVID : How do you swallow that ?
Snap !
You got snapped on by Weird Al .
If I 'd survived a shark attack , you 'd be gushing over every gory detail .
Begging me to show the teeth marks .
God , no . Horrendous .
Are you telling me there 's no difference between Michael Myers and a shark ?
LOOMIS : Of course there is . Good God , don 't be ridiculous .
YANKOVIC : I 'm a little confused .
Are we talking about the Austin Powers Mike Myers
- or is this - - ? - It 's over .
Mya !
( MAN SINGING DAY OF THE DEAD )
COFFINS : Looking for me ? Ha-ha-ha .
LAURIE : Do you know where Mya is ?
( LAURIE GRUNTING )
♪ ♪
What do you want from me ?
It 's almost time to come home , Angel .
Is she ready ?
Soon .
( LAURIE SCREAMING )
MYA : Laurie , Laurie .
Hey , hey ! It 's me , it 's Mya .
- Come on . - Oh , fuck .
Step . Steppity-steppity-step .
Hey , I so wanna go back in .
- And I wanna - - - No , no , no .
- No . We 're going home . - Hey .
Where 's Harley ?
I don 't know .
- See , we need to go back in and - - - No .
She went to go hang out with some dude like she always does .
She 'll find her way home .
( PHONE RINGING )
Hello ?
BRACKETT ( OVER PHONE ) : Hey , sweetie .
Seriously , Dad . Please stop calling .
- Okay ? - Oh . Okay .
I know you love me .
Oh , God . I love you too .
♪ ♪
( ANDY GRUNTING )
( ANNIE SOBBING AND SCREAMING )
( GLASS SHATTERING )
( THUDS AND MICHAEL GRUNTING )
MYA : I 'm glad you decided to come home .
Running away never solves anything . Trust me , I 've tried .
LAURIE : I 'm sure they have their reasons for not telling me .
Figure it out in the morning .
Hey , world !
Guess what .
I 'm Michael Myers ' sister !
I 'm so fucked !
What am I gonna do , dude ?
Just take it one day at a time .
One day at a time .
- Annie was right . - MYA : Maybe she 's a genius .
Home sweet home .
♪ ♪
The place is , like , spinning .
- Want some tea ? - Yeah . What you got ?
- Blended black / green tea ? - Uh-uh .
- Berry blossom - - - Yeah , berry .
- Does it have caffeine in it ? - Yeah .
No . Dude , I can 't fucking read that ?
Oh , yeah , it does .
It 's okay . I 'll sleep like a baby after what we went through tonight .
Mmm . These cookies are so good . You should have a cookie .
It 'll help soak up all that alcohol rotting in your gut .
Ugh . Don 't think a cookie is gonna save me .
Oh , my head .
What the fuck ?
Annie ?
( ANNIE SCREAMING )
( ANNIE SOBBING )
Annie ?
No , please .
( GRUNTING )
Now go have some fun .
Okay .
Annie ?
- Annie ! Aah ! Aah ! Aah ! - MYA : Oh , my God .
- No , baby ! - MYA : Oh , my God !
( LAURIE MYA SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY )
Mya , Mya , Mya !
I need you to calm down .
I need you to call 911 . Please ? I need you to call 911 .
Go ! Go !
Oh , my God ! Annie !
Oh , my God , baby .
Fuck .
Baby .
Oh , my God .
There 's a girl in the , um - -
She 's upstairs , she 's - -
I don 't know - - I don 't know if she 's okay .
She may be dead , but there 's blood everywhere .
Stay with me . Please stay with me . Please .
Please , I need you , okay ?
Oh , my God .
Oh , my God , I need you so much .
Baby , I 'm so sorry .
Mya , hurry !
I don 't know . I 'm on Cherrywood Road , I 'm not at home .
I 'm at - - Maybe it 's avenue , uh - - Hold on .
Stay on the line . It 's Cherrywood , I know that .
It 's - - We 're at 1-5 - - We 're at 15 Cherry - -
( MYA SCREAMING )
Mya ?
( MYA GRUNTS )
( WHIMPERING )
Mya , what 's happening ? !
It is him . Please go .
LAURIE : I 'm not leaving you .
Baby , I 'm gonna put you down .
- ANNIE : No . - I 'm gonna put you down .
ANNIE : No .
( ANNIE GROANING )
LAURIE : Okay .
Okay . Hold on , baby , hold on .
You know , Annie 's gonna smell this on my clothes and kill me .
Sheriff Brackett .
I just got a 911 phone call .
- So did you dispatch ? - Yes , sir , I did .
- So why are you telling me about it ? - Because , sir ,
the phone call came from your house .
No .
LAURIE : Please , baby , please .
- I 'm gonna stay right here . - It 's okay .
No , baby , no . I 'm not leaving you .
- ANNIE : It 's okay . Go . - No , I 'm not gonna leave you .
Baby ? Baby ? Baby ?
( ANNIE COUGHING )
Annie ?
Annie ? Stay with me .
Stay with me . Stay with me , baby . Stay with me , okay ?
You gotta stay with me . You gotta .
Annie , stay with me .
( LAURIE CRYING )
Annie ?
Annie ? Annie ?
♪ ♪
Annie ?
Don 't leave me , baby .
( THUDDING )
Annie .
( LAURIE SCREAMING )
( GASPS )
( SIREN WAILING )
Please , sheriff , you don 't wanna go in there . I - - Let me handle this .
Where is she ?
You don 't wanna go in there , sheriff .
BRACKETT : No .
Oh , God .
( MOANING )
Oh , no . Annie .
Annie ! God , no .
God , please .
Oh , God . No !
No !
( SCREAMING INAUDIBLY )
♪ ♪
( WHIMPERING )
Stop !
Stop , please !
Please stop !
Stop ! Please !
Stop !
Please ! Please stop !
Stop , please !
Stop !
( PANTING )
Stop .
Please stop . Stop , please .
( VOID 'S " TIME TO DIE " PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS )
Stop .
MAN : Hey .
Hey .
- Are you okay ? - He 's coming . Please .
- He 's coming . He 's coming . - No one 's coming .
- It 's okay . - He 's - - He 's gonna kill me .
- Please ! - It 's okay .
I gotta take you to a hospital , okay ?
We 're gonna go to a hospital , and everything 's okay .
It 's okay . It 's okay .
- LAURIE : Hurry . - It 's okay .
It 's okay . It 's okay . It 's okay .
You 're all right . You 're all right . It 's okay .
( LAURIE AND JIMMY SCREAM )
( SCREAMING )
( HORN HONKING )
( FIRE CRACKLING )
( CAR DOOR OPENS )
♪ ♪
Chief .
We got another body up on Eagle Road .
We got a witness .
She saw a large man carrying a girl away from a crash .
The state police believe the perp is barricaded inside of a shack
just north of the crash site .
Okay .
Want me to handle it ?
( GRUNTING )
- I think maybe you should drive . - Yes , sir .
People , roll out . Going to Eagle Road .
Who are you ?
You know who I am , Angel .
Now ,
repeat after me :
I love you , Mommy .
( WHISPERS ) I love you , Mommy .
Mommy , I love you ! Please ! Please don 't !
Let me go ! Let me go !
♪ ♪
BRACKETT ( ON BULLHORN ) : You are surrounded .
Come out with your hands up .
- Help ! Help , please ! - BRACKETT : I repeat .
You are surrounded .
- Come out with your hands up . - LAURIE : Don 't ! Please !
MAN 1 ( ON TV ) : - - treasury purchases today to keep that 10-year yield below 3 percent .
That 's a big issue . When stock traders start talking about treasury yields , pay attention .
You 're an asshole .
MAN 2 : This is breaking news .
MAN 3 : This is Chopper 2 . I wanna take you below .
This situation is just incredible . I can 't believe what I 'm reporting ,
but a man who police believe to be deceased serial killer Michael Myers
has taken a hostage , now identified as Laurie Strode .
Miss Strode allegedly shot and killed Myers herself
after being abducted on Halloween night .
And as if this story couldn 't get more twisted , it was revealed earlier today - -
God , no .
BRACKETT ( ON BULLHORN ) : Come out with your hands up .
You 're surrounded .
OFFICER 1 : Tell me you got a shot , Caleb .
- No , I can 't get a clean shot . - Damn it .
In the shack . You 're surrounded .
There is no escape .
Come out with your hands up .
- Waste of fucking time . - Chief .
No sniper has a clean shot .
OFFICER 2 : Hey , hey , hey ! Get this vehicle out of here .
Sir , get back in the car .
- BRACKETT : Hold this . - Sheriff !
Sheriff .
( LOOMIS GRUNTS )
BRACKETT : Get up . Get up .
There 's an innocent girl in there I might have kept safe
but for your greedy fucking book .
I wanna shoot you . I wanna shoot you so bad .
I wanna shoot him . I wanna shoot him !
- I wanna fucking shoot him ! - OFFICER 3 : Sheriff , please .
You son of a bitch ! You don 't deserve to live .
Please , I just
came here because I wanted to help .
There is nothing that you have to say
that I wanna hear .
Sheriff , please .
You must trust me .
Look , this is pointless .
Michael 's never gonna respond to hostage negotiations .
Get him the fuck out of here .
Listen , I can draw him out .
I can draw him out . I need to do this .
- Please , let me do this . - Get him the fuck out of here !
All right , all right , all right ! I can walk from here , okay .
Get out of there !
Sheriff ! I owe you .
- I owe you this . - Goddamn it !
- Stand down ! - OFFICER 4 : Stand down !
♪ ♪
( LAURIE WHIMPERING )
Michael .
She ...
needs to come with me .
- Come on . - I - - I can 't .
He 's holding me down .
What ?
Listen to me , Laurie . There 's no one holding you down .
Let me go !
Listen to me , Laurie , listen ! Stop !
- Listen to me ! - LAURIE : Let go of me !
Stop it !
- Stop ! It 's all in your mind . - No ! No !
- It 's all in your mind ! - Let me go !
- We are ready . - Stop !
- DEBORAH : It is time , Michael . - Stop !
- Take us home . - Stop !
Stop !
Michael , for God in hell ... .
Die !
( GRUNTS )
( HELICOPTER WHIRRING )
Now !
( SHOUTING INAUDIBLY )
♪ ♪
( GUNSHOTS )
Hold your fire ! Hold your fire !
♪ ♪
( NAN VERNON 'S " LOVE HURTS " PLAYING )